Do you think
Penny's right?
(Leonard:)Were we bullying Zack?
(Sheldon:)No,
(Howard:)I know bullying.
(Howard:)He left here unswirlied and his
ass crack was underpants-free.
(Raj:)And nobody drew
a penis on his forehead.
(Leonard:)That happened to you?
(Raj:)First day of cricket camp.
(Raj:)They drew it
so the testicles were my eyes.
(Leonard:)I don't know, I think
we might owe the guy an apology.
(Howard:)So go apologize.
Why me?
(Howard:)You started it,
we just piled on.
(Leonard:)What would I even say?
(Sheldon:)Zack, I'm sorry you're stupid.
(Sheldon:)Have a Milk Dud.
(Raj:)A Milk Dud?
Yeah,
(Sheldon:)Milk Duds,
with their self-deprecating name
and remarkably mild flavor,
(Sheldon:)are the most apologetic
of the boxed candies.
(Leonard:)I got a better idea.
(Leonard:)We're all responsible.
(Leonard:)I say we all go.